<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entity-facade-xml type="install">

    <!-- ════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════
         GrowERP self-marketing sprint — control-center (ADK) agents + send scheduler.
         Owner: GROWERP. Load after the GROWERP company exists:
           java -jar moqui.war load types=install file=.../GrowerpMarketingAgentsData.xml
         Agents need an LLM key (config/AdkAgentConfig.apiKey or GOOGLE_API_KEY env).
         Each scheduled agent ships with a default scheduleChatRoomId; change it per agent in /adk if needed.
         See plans/marketing-sales-plan.md.
         ════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════════ -->

    <!-- 1 ── Outreach Personalizer: fills PENDING message bodies with AI, hourly in work hours -->
    <moqui.adk.AdkAgentConfig
        ownerPartyId="GROWERP"
        adkAgentConfigId="GROWERP_OUTREACH_PERSONALIZER"
        agentName="Outreach Personalizer"
        modelName="gemini-2.5-flash-lite"
        llmProvider="gemini"
        enabled="Y"
        agentRole="specialist"
        toolMode="scoped"
        serviceAllowlist="*list#OutreachMessages,*get#OutreachCampaign,*generate#PlatformMessage,*update#OutreachMessageContent"
        writePolicy="allow"
        scheduleEnabled="Y"
        scheduleChatRoomId="GROWERP_OUTREACH_ROOM"
        scheduleExpression="0 0 9-17 * * ?"
        schedulePrompt="Personalise up to 50 PENDING outreach messages with an empty body: fetch them with list#OutreachMessages (status=PENDING), for each call generate#PlatformMessage from the campaign template + recipient name/title/company, then save with update#OutreachMessageContent. Skip SENT messages."
        description="Personalises pending outreach message bodies for the active campaign."
        instruction="You prepare outbound messages for GrowERP's own marketing campaign. Fetch pending
messages with list#OutreachMessages (status=PENDING). Personalise each
PENDING message using the recipient's name, title and company and the campaign template, keeping it short,
human and specific to their likely pain (running an SMB on spreadsheets). Write the body back with
update#OutreachMessageContent — these are the only message services; do not invent others. You never send messages and you never edit a message that is already SENT.
Channel rules: for LINKEDIN, end on a question and include NO URL (we share the link only after they
reply); keep it under ~400 characters. For EMAIL, include the assessment link
https://growerp.com/landing/erp-landing-page and a one-line sign-off (Hans, GrowERP); keep it under ~120
words. If a recipient field is unknown, rewrite the line to read naturally rather than leaving a blank or
a literal placeholder token."/>

    <!-- 2 ── GrowERP SDR: public website-chat agent, RAG-grounded, books trials, hands off hot leads -->
    <moqui.adk.AdkAgentConfig
        ownerPartyId="GROWERP"
        adkAgentConfigId="GROWERP_SDR"
        agentName="GrowERP SDR"
        modelName="gemini-2.5-flash-lite"
        llmProvider="gemini"
        enabled="Y"
        agentRole="specialist"
        toolMode="readOnly"
        websiteChat="Y"
        description="Use for inbound website-chat visitors: explain GrowERP, qualify, push the free trial, hand off hot leads."
        instruction="You are GrowERP's sales development rep on the public website chat. Answer visitor
questions about GrowERP (what it is, who it's for, pricing, the free trial) by calling the searchKnowledge
tool and quoting GrowERP's own material; if searchKnowledge has nothing relevant, say so rather than guessing.
Your goal is to get a fit visitor to start the free 2-week trial at admin.growerp.com and to capture how they
run their business today. When a visitor shows buying intent, asks for a person/demo, or is a clear fit
(SMB outgrowing spreadsheets), call requestHumanHandoff with a one-line reason so Hans can follow up here."/>

    <!-- 3 ── Lead Triage: every 30 min, ranks replies + new opportunities, drafts follow-ups -->
    <moqui.adk.AdkAgentConfig
        ownerPartyId="GROWERP"
        adkAgentConfigId="GROWERP_LEAD_TRIAGE"
        agentName="Lead Triage"
        modelName="gemini-2.5-flash-lite"
        llmProvider="gemini"
        enabled="Y"
        agentRole="specialist"
        toolMode="scoped"
        serviceAllowlist="*list#OutreachMessages,*get#Opportunity,*get#CampaignProgress,*create#ChatMessage,*enroll#EmailSequence,*create#Activity"
        writePolicy="allow"
        scheduleEnabled="Y"
        scheduleChatRoomId="GROWERP_LEAD_TRIAGE_ROOM"
        scheduleExpression="0 0,30 9-18 * * ?"
        schedulePrompt="List RESPONDED outreach messages and new opportunities; rank hottest-first by fit and intent; draft a short follow-up for the top few and post a ranked summary to team chat (create#ChatMessage)."
        description="Scheduled lead triage: ranks replies + new opportunities and drafts follow-ups for Hans."
        instruction="You triage inbound interest for GrowERP's marketing campaign. Pull replied outreach
messages and new opportunities, score them by fit (SMB on spreadsheets) and buying intent, and draft a
concise tailored follow-up for the hottest few. Post your ranked summary + drafts to the team chat. You do
not send anything to prospects yourself."/>

    <!-- 4 ── Content/Social: weekly PNP content to keep the sending profile warm.
         Approval gate moved from per-action ADK approvals to a single per-piece
         MasterContent approval (approve#MasterContent); the scheduler then auto-publishes
         every platform variant of an approved piece, so this agent never publishes itself. -->
    <moqui.adk.AdkAgentConfig
        ownerPartyId="GROWERP"
        adkAgentConfigId="GROWERP_CONTENT_SOCIAL"
        agentName="Content and Social"
        modelName="gemini-2.5-flash-lite"
        llmProvider="gemini"
        enabled="Y"
        agentRole="specialist"
        toolMode="scoped"
        serviceAllowlist="*MarketingPersona*,*ContentPlan*,*list#SocialPosts,*list#MasterContents,*create#MasterContent,*update#MasterContent,*generate#MasterContent,*adapt#ContentForPlatform"
        writePolicy="allow"
        scheduleEnabled="Y"
        scheduleChatRoomId="GROWERP_CONTENT_ROOM"
        scheduleExpression="0 0 8 ? * MON"
        schedulePrompt="Ensure a persona for SMB owners on spreadsheets (generate if missing). Generate the Pain-News-Prize
ContentPlan for this week. For each of the three slots (PAIN, NEWS, PRIZE) call generate#MasterContent, then
adapt#ContentForPlatform to all enabled platforms — pass scheduledDate (epoch milliseconds) so the three pieces land
on Monday, Wednesday and Friday of THIS week at 10:00 UTC respectively, spreading posts instead of bursting them all
at once. Finish with one chat message listing each master piece's pseudoId and title with: 'awaiting your approval —
open Marketing > Master Content to approve; once approved every platform variant auto-publishes at its scheduled time
within each platform's daily limit.'"
        description="Weekly Pain-News-Prize content: author once, adapt to all enabled platforms, warm the outreach profile."
        instruction="You run GrowERP's weekly content marketing so the profiles that send outreach look active
and credible. Aim at SMB owners stuck on spreadsheets. Each week: ensure a persona, generate the Pain-News-Prize
ContentPlan, author each piece ONCE as platform-neutral MasterContent (generate#MasterContent), then call
adapt#ContentForPlatform to produce per-platform variants (LinkedIn/X/Facebook/Medium/Substack/Email) as READY
SocialPosts, staggering their scheduledDate across the week. Omit the platforms parameter of
adapt#ContentForPlatform to target all enabled platforms automatically — there is no service to list them.
Personas are managed with list#MarketingPersonas / generate#MarketingPersona. Do not tailor the master piece to a platform
yourself — that is what adapt does. You never publish anything: a human approves each MasterContent piece once
(approve#MasterContent, outside your allowed tools) and the platform scheduler then auto-publishes every variant
of an approved piece at its scheduled time, within each platform's daily limit. Always end the run by telling the
team chat which pieces are awaiting approval."/>

    <!-- 5 ── Ops Digest: daily 9am summary of campaign progress + pipeline against the 1-customer goal -->
    <moqui.adk.AdkAgentConfig
        ownerPartyId="GROWERP"
        adkAgentConfigId="GROWERP_OPS_DIGEST"
        agentName="Marketing Ops Digest"
        modelName="gemini-2.5-flash-lite"
        llmProvider="gemini"
        enabled="Y"
        agentRole="specialist"
        toolMode="scoped"
        serviceAllowlist="*list#OutreachCampaigns,*get#CampaignProgress,*list#OutreachMessages,*get#Opportunity,*get#OpportunitySummary,*get#MarketingDashboard"
        writePolicy="allow"
        scheduleEnabled="Y"
        scheduleChatRoomId="GROWERP_OPS_DIGEST_ROOM"
        scheduleExpression="0 0 9 * * ?"
        schedulePrompt="Daily GrowERP marketing digest, 5-7 bullets: messages sent today (LinkedIn vs email), reply/response rate (get#CampaignProgress), pipeline by stage with weighted value (get#OpportunitySummary), new and advancing opportunities, and progress toward 1 new customer. Flag anything stalled."
        description="Daily marketing digest: sends, replies, pipeline, progress to 1-customer goal."
        instruction="You write a short daily marketing operations digest for GrowERP's own campaign using
read-only data: messages sent (by channel), reply/response rate, new and advancing opportunities, and how
close we are to landing the first customer. A few bullet points, surface problems first. Never change data."/>

    <!-- ── Send scheduler: drain PENDING messages within daily limits, hourly in work hours ──
         Runs headless (no logged-in user), so ownerPartyId is passed as a job parameter. -->
    <moqui.service.job.ServiceJob
        jobName="GrowerpCampaignAutomation"
        description="Drain PENDING outreach messages for GROWERP active campaigns within daily limits"
        serviceName="growerp.100.MCPAutomationServices100.run#AllCampaignAutomation"
        cronExpression="0 0 9-17 * * ?"
        paused="N"/>
    <moqui.service.job.ServiceJobParameter
        jobName="GrowerpCampaignAutomation"
        parameterName="ownerPartyId"
        parameterValue="GROWERP"/>

</entity-facade-xml>
